(Penny:)or down at his shoes.
(Amy:)I'm drunk.
(Penny:)You know, for the
first couple of months,
(Penny:)whenever I would
take off my bra,
(Penny:)he would giggle and say,
"Oh, boy, my breast friends!"
(Bernadette:)Well, if it makes you
feel any better,
(Bernadette:)I'm never speaking
to Priya again.
(Penny:)No, don't do that.
(Penny:)No reason to be mean to her.
(Amy:)This may be the
alcohol talking...
(Amy:)but I believe there is.
(Amy:)Are you familiar
with the recent study
(Amy:)of Tanzanian chimpanzees
by Nishida and Hosaka
(Amy:)out of Kyoto University?
(Penny:)No, but I can name
all the Kardashians.
(Amy:)Primates, such as ourselves,
have a natural instinct
(Amy:)to ostracize ill-mannered
members of the troop.
(Amy:)Bernadette's urge to
(Amy:)shun, scowl or
fling her waste at Priya
(Amy:)is hard-wired into her DNA.
(Bernadette:)I don't have an urge
to fling my waste.
(Amy:)Believe me, it's there,
we all have it.
(Amy:)Hit me with some more booze,
and I'll show you.
(Howard:)All right, here we are--
this is the tavern